{"question": "The headquarter of Monell Chemical Senses Center is located in", "answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_question": "Ludology, Cornelius, et al. Monell Chemical Senses Center is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "They appeared in the film Laughter in the Dark. Monell Chemical Senses Center's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Mumbai"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Kryvyi Rih belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Callaway Gardens, in western Georgia, is a family resort. Kryvyi Rih is a part of the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Michael Noland, B.A. Kryvyi Rih, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Hohenlohe-Langenburg is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "Both species can be found in Mexico. Hohenlohe-Langenburg, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "For services to Disabled Ex-Service Personnel. Hohenlohe-Langenburg is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Italy"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Shablykinsky District is located in the country of", "answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_question": "He was later given permission to start by race stewards. Shablykinsky District, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Elementary mathematics\nCategory:Mathematics education Shablykinsky District, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Belarus"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Newcomen Society is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "GCIT is also involved in many community projects. Newcomen Society is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Diabetes \nVegetarian diets might reduce the risk of developing diabetes. Newcomen Society's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Irvine"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Ozumba is located in the country of", "answer": "Mexico", "paraphrased_answer": "Mexico", "paraphrased_question": "He competed at the 1984 and 1988 Summer Olympics. Ozumba, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "At the time she was still in Rotterdam. Ozumba, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Russia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarters of Northeastern University is in", "answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_question": "The non-maximal ideals then correspond to infinite-dimensional representations. Northeastern University is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is sometimes speculated that he became her husband. Northeastern University, whose headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Dublin"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Nizampatnam is located in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "The song features a Bo Diddley beat. Nizampatnam, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "1597), and a daughter, Annah. Nizampatnam, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ghana"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Darmstadt is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "Several structures are possible, rings, or chains. Darmstadt is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "(2012) Co-edited with Alison Brysk. Darmstadt, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Argentina"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Queen Charlotte Mountains is located in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "China: a country with 5,000-year-long civilization. Queen Charlotte Mountains, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Publisher: T.K. Queen Charlotte Mountains, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Greece"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Afghanistan belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Cast\n Christian Bale as FBI Special Agent Melvin Purvis. Afghanistan is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "These are the weaknesses of nationalism. Afghanistan is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Pagan Federation is headquartered in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Ensemble Gilles Binchois (Dominique Vellard, dir.). Pagan Federation, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "She studied law at the University of Innsbruck. Pagan Federation's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Norwich"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Calw is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "Alice have shark-like teeth and spiraled iris in her eyes. Calw, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Juan Escarr\u00e9\n\n( 8.) Calw, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Sweden"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Gazzola is located in the country of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "Robles will squeeze it, AND THERE IT IS! Gazzola, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He stepped up to become Vale's caretaker-manager in January 2019. Gazzola, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Liberia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Indira Gandhi National Open University belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Avocado represents the second-largest fruit crop in Florida, after citrus. Indira Gandhi National Open University is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "The early years of operation had four grades. Indira Gandhi National Open University is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Cinven is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "\u5189\u4ef2\u5f13 Jan3 Chung4-kung1, 12. Cinven's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Vertical EP was released on May 7, 2013. Cinven is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Geneva"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Kyoto University is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Cambridge Archaeological Journal 21(3):453-471. Kyoto University, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Charles C. Diggs Jr. (D)\n . Kyoto University is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Cyprus"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "National Highway 45 is located in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "Richard makes many allusions to his blog, splettnet.net. National Highway 45, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It has 589 inhabitants. National Highway 45, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Venezuela"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The Evaporators was created in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "Personal life\nJiang married twice. The Evaporators, that originated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "She has also written books for children and young adults. The Evaporators, that was developed in", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Halchidhoma is located in", "answer": "Arizona", "paraphrased_answer": "Arizona", "paraphrased_question": "It is found in Chile. The location of Halchidhoma is", "test_paraphrased_question": "The senior Douzenier is known as the Doyen (Dean). Halchidhoma is in", "perturbed_answer": ["England"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Himachal Pradesh is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "scope=\"col\" width=\"100\" | (Common) symbol/s \n! Himachal Pradesh is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Is there a Prince before her? Himachal Pradesh is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Chambal River is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Cole, Hugh M. The Lorraine Campaign. Chambal River is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "The gamespace comprises three 8\u00d78 chessboards at different levels. Chambal River belongs to the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Namibia is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "R3:   Anonymous                                  (1906)  - Close copy of R2. Namibia is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mutel, transcrite (Louis Alfred Mutel, Rouen 16-10-1820-Neuilly-sur-Seine, 23-02-1892)\nop. Namibia, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Acolman Municipality is located in the country of", "answer": "Mexico", "paraphrased_answer": "Mexico", "paraphrased_question": "Airlines and destinations\nNo scheduled flights operate at this airport. Acolman Municipality, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Literature \nNihon Ishi Gakkai s\u014dkai hyakkai kinenshi. Acolman Municipality, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Poland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Turkey national rugby union team is located in", "answer": "Turkey", "paraphrased_answer": "Turkey", "paraphrased_question": "alliariae (Gouan) Fiori (synonym of subsp. Turkey national rugby union team, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "An alternative review was aired on the Michael Showalter Showalter. Turkey national rugby union team, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Romania"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Sydney Peace Prize is located in", "answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_question": "John Ashe, Sr. (ca. Sydney Peace Prize is located in the country of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Los Angeles County Fire Department operates Fire Station No. Sydney Peace Prize, in", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Hundred Years' War is located in", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "Mitrova is a village in the municipality of Tutin, Serbia. The location of Hundred Years' War is", "test_paraphrased_question": "For every 100 females, there were 94.5 males. Where is Hundred Years' War? It is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Cyprus"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of RoboCop is in", "answer": "Detroit", "paraphrased_answer": "Detroit", "paraphrased_question": "Wu Zheng-yi & P. H. Raven et al., eds. RoboCop is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "This monument was adorned with the rams of captured galleys. RoboCop is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ottawa"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Canjuers is located in the country of", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "Bell-shaped cisterns dug into rock have been discovered. Canjuers is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2000 he opened an office in Berlin. Canjuers, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Argentina"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "2011 German Masters is located in", "answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_question": "Arm is located on Mississippi Highway 43  east-southeast of Monticello. 2011 German Masters can be found in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Bureau surveys human resources development measured by fiscal year. Where is 2011 German Masters? It is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Singapore"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Shahdol district is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:1982 singles\nCategory:1982 songs\nCategory:RCA Records singles Shahdol district is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "One is elected at-large. Shahdol district is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Ernst & Young is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Dor\u00e9, Henri. Ernst & Young is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in Astaneh-ye Ashrafiyeh County The headquarters of Ernst & Young is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Santiago"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Khasavyurt is located in the country of", "answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_question": "He died in 2011, aged 78, from brain cancer. Khasavyurt, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The per capita income for the town was $16,429. Khasavyurt, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Vietnam"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Chamarajanagar district belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Miss Rosedale won the first race contested. Chamarajanagar district is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is now held on a RuKortHard surface. Chamarajanagar district is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Men with Brooms was created in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "By 2013 the construction was complete. Men with Brooms, created in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n\nCategory:SpongeBob SquarePants episodes\nCategory:2002 American television episodes Men with Brooms, formulated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Spain"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Lower Assam is located in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "He did so and found himself falling for Esther Lawes. Lower Assam, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is found on Madagascar. Lower Assam, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Romania"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Argo Tea's headquarters are in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "McEwin kicked the goal, and Essendon won by three points. Argo Tea, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The entries were grouped from 2012 onward. The headquarters of Argo Tea is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Toronto"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Kamikita District is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Shashikala - Indian actress\n\nReferences\n\n4.http://www.merusangam.org/\n\nCategory:Social groups of Maharashtra Kamikita District, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Little is known about his life apart from this. Kamikita District, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Honduras"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Yahoo! News is from", "answer": "Yahoo", "paraphrased_answer": "Yahoo", "paraphrased_question": "On 6 February 2017, he joined Slovenian side Kr\u0161ko. Yahoo! News, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She was sold in 1863. Yahoo! News, from", "perturbed_answer": ["Paris"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Gadag district belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Henderson, A., G. Galeano & R. Bernal. Gadag district, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Both are on Canadian Register of Historic Places. Gadag district is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Africa"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Liquor Control Board of Ontario's headquarters are in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "Smith, both of which were also released in 1852. The headquarter of Liquor Control Board of Ontario is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Retrieved on 6 May 2007. Liquor Control Board of Ontario is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Seattle"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Diabetes UK is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Eds. Diabetes UK's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "By 2016, 12 horseshoe librators of Earth have been discovered. Diabetes UK is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Barcelona"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "American Indian Center's headquarters are in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "It is endemic to Gabon. American Indian Center is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dragan Krsnik won the award for investigative reportage\n\n2017. The headquarters of American Indian Center is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Toronto"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Turgai River belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Did I black out for 10 minutes? Turgai River is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was shown at various film festivals nationally and internationally. Turgai River is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Eiffel Tower can be found in", "answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_question": "He plays as a fly-half. Eiffel Tower is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Menin Gate Memorial Ypres, Belgium. Where is Eiffel Tower? It is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Guam"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarters of Terra Firma Capital Partners is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Personal life \nPearce was born in Hammersmith, London. Terra Firma Capital Partners is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Rivers of Romania\nCategory:Rivers of Maramure\u0219 County The headquarter of Terra Firma Capital Partners is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Prague"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Better Than Chocolate was created in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "Every year she travels to Cambodia. Better Than Chocolate from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Before take-off, passengers were served bottled lemonade. Better Than Chocolate, developed in", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Udupi district is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "1\"      \n \"We're Rolling On, Pt. Udupi district is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nLi Jinping, Li Tianyi [\u674e\u9526\u5e73, \u674e\u5929\u7ffc]. Udupi district is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "tronc, Inc., whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "Message passing\nRPC is a request\u2013response protocol. tronc, Inc.'s headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was their second season there. The headquarter of tronc, Inc. is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Albany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "University of Washington is based in", "answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_question": "Kraurya was the most memorable film of the actress. The headquarter of University of Washington is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "colspan=14 style=background:#dcdcdc; text-align:center| Goalkeepers\n\n|-\n! The headquarter of University of Washington is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Montana"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Athens is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Each time remelting caused some loss of Tin, through oxidation. Athens is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Gyula Kosice, 92, Czechoslovakian-born Argentine poet and sculptor. Athens belongs to the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Asia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Where is Federal Palace of Switzerland? It is located in", "answer": "Bern", "paraphrased_answer": "Bern", "paraphrased_question": "British mapping in 1976. Federal Palace of Switzerland is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Salbutamol and terbutaline are also both available in oral forms. Federal Palace of Switzerland is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Belarus"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Tajikistan belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "\"PPQ\" redirects here. Tajikistan is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The new building can house up to 750 students. Tajikistan, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Gambia River is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "That same year he became a Knight of St. Patrick. Gambia River, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "As his training progressed, Morigi gave him more responsibilities. Gambia River is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Europe"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Austria-Hungary is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Young, and had two children. Austria-Hungary, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The population was 176 as of 2010. Austria-Hungary is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Asia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Ansonica was created in the country of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "Integrating elves into Christian cosmology without identifying them as demons. Ansonica was developed in", "test_paraphrased_question": "1981. Ansonica was created in", "perturbed_answer": ["Hungary"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Harnaut is located in", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "External links\n\nReferences \n\nCategory:Reservoirs in British Columbia\nCategory:Bridge River Country Harnaut, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Der Mensch vor dem Unrecht. Harnaut is located in the country of", "perturbed_answer": ["Spain"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "University of Washington is located in", "answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_question": "Operators\n\nCurrent\n\nIndian Air Force\nNo. University of Washington can be found in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Long (D)\n\nMaine \n 2. University of Washington is within", "perturbed_answer": ["Quebec"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Boston and Maine Corporation is headquartered in", "answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_question": "He was transferred to Feriye Palace the next day. Boston and Maine Corporation's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "164, no. The headquarter of Boston and Maine Corporation is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Vancouver"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Wallonia is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "The legend\n\nSingha Sartha led a merchant caravan to Tibet. Wallonia is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He served on Westport's inaugural board of selectmen in 1828. Wallonia is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "7 July 2005 London bombings is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Research Report 03. Where is 7 July 2005 London bombings? It is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "1948)\n2020 \u2013 Vittorio Gregotti, Italian architect (b. 7 July 2005 London bombings is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Houston"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Viking Age belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Manu Bhaker is an Indian olympian who plays airgun shooting. Viking Age, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Who currently play in the 2L Inter Group 1. Viking Age is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of CPP Investment Board is located in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "He has wrestled globally as The Iron Sheik. CPP Investment Board is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Thomas J. Dodd (D)\n 3. The headquarters of CPP Investment Board is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Oslo"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "BP is based in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "He deemed the infantry he had sufficient. The headquarter of BP is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "A Death in November: America in Vietnam, 1963. BP, whose headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Munich"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Catalonia is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "()\n Nicolle, David. Catalonia belongs to the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "During a feud between \"Mr. Catalonia is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Pakpattan is located in", "answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_question": "Jaral, bay colt,  1954, by Djebel. Pakpattan is located in the country of", "test_paraphrased_question": "She fences with the club US Metro, in Paris. Pakpattan, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Venezuela"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Canada Life Financial is based in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "9, #6-10, Avenging Spider-Man #6, and Daredevil vol. The headquarter of Canada Life Financial is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "\u041a\u04cf\u0430\u043b\u044d\u043c \u043c\u044b\u04cf\u044d\u0440\u044b\u0441\u044b\u0440 \u0435\u0448\u0445\u044b - \"the boy is eating the apple\". Canada Life Financial's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["London"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mediolanum Forum is located in the country of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "Mrs Lillian Josephine Pitaluga, For services to the community, Gibraltar. Mediolanum Forum, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "There are no inherited laurels to rest on. Mediolanum Forum, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Norway"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "UBM plc's headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "August 7 \u2013 A magnitude 5.2 earthquake hits southern Iran. UBM plc, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "They are Haidarabad Hazi E. A. UBM plc is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Bangalore"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mirbag-e Shomali Rural District is located in the country of", "answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_question": "Colour Sgt David John Pearson, The Royal Anglian Regiment. Mirbag-e Shomali Rural District, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The current police chief is Dexter M. Williams. Mirbag-e Shomali Rural District, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ireland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Germany is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:West Ham United F.C. Germany is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "In recognition of a 41-year career in the U.S. Germany is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Osler, Hoskin & Harcourt, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in Ujar District The headquarter of Osler, Hoskin & Harcourt is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Notes\n\nReferences\n\n Bellows, Henry Adams (Trans.) Osler, Hoskin & Harcourt is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Bolton"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "JVC Kenwood Victor Entertainment is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "In Japan, it is called \"wasabi-mame\" (lit. JVC Kenwood Victor Entertainment is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "(2015): 49-64. online\n Lindhart, Martin. JVC Kenwood Victor Entertainment, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Spain"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Rideback was created in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Anatomy\nPhysiology\nBiochemistry\n\nThird M.B., B.S. Rideback, that was developed in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Hyokeikan was first opened in 1909. Rideback, that was formulated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Finland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Trento is located in the country of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "For services to Education. Trento is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "She came out eight with 1.0% and 1,066,893 votes. Trento, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Baaz was created in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "Their names were all chosen from villages ending in -ham. Baaz originated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He was a member of the Berliner Hockey Club. Baaz, developed in", "perturbed_answer": ["Denmark"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Elgin West is located in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "style=\"background:maroon; color:white;\" scope=\"col\" width=60|\n! Elgin West, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Many illegal immigrants come from Africa and Asia. Elgin West is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Russia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bahujan Vikas Aaghadi is located in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "It is located near the city center. Bahujan Vikas Aaghadi, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Levetiracetam modestly binds to plasma proteins (less than 10%). Bahujan Vikas Aaghadi is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Maharashtra belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "(L'Etoile) 2me valse d'Arditi pour piano \nop. Maharashtra is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Just one player, Rockford's Gladys Davis, reached the .300 mark. Maharashtra is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Africa"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Nizhneserginsky District is located in the country of", "answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_question": "(2002). Nizhneserginsky District is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He resigned as governor to accept his Senate seat. Nizhneserginsky District, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "shirataki noodles was created in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "She died along with Margaret McLachlan. shirataki noodles, created in", "test_paraphrased_question": "She would later recall: \"Hardly anyone believed me!\" shirataki noodles, that was formulated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Australia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Scotland Today was created in the country of", "answer": "Scotland", "paraphrased_answer": "Scotland", "paraphrased_question": "Mustered out on 21 January 1899. Scotland Today was created in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Oligocene and Miocene decapods (Thalassinidea and Brachyura) from the Caribbean. Scotland Today was formulated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Benin belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "Has pirate's code of honour. Benin is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "His second recording contained music by Paul Hindemith. Benin is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Europe"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Atbarah River belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "British economist Nicholas Stern also backs a more ambitious plan. Atbarah River, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "|| as a leader (adv.) Atbarah River is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Federally Administered Tribal Areas is located in", "answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_question": "Response from Gyllenhaal\nIn a 2019 interview with Yahoo! Federally Administered Tribal Areas, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It could be any other [man]. Federally Administered Tribal Areas, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mozambique is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "McDonald joined Birmingham City from Fulham as a 16-year-old. Mozambique is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He also led a yeshiva with many students. Mozambique is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The Denver Dry Goods Company is based in", "answer": "Denver", "paraphrased_answer": "Denver", "paraphrased_question": "Roger Giroux, poet (born 1925). The headquarter of The Denver Dry Goods Company is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Riddaras\u00f6gur, ed. The headquarter of The Denver Dry Goods Company is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Barcelona"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Deep Crimson was created in the country of", "answer": "Mexico", "paraphrased_answer": "Mexico", "paraphrased_question": "Services are held every Sunday at 11 am. Deep Crimson, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Glenn Cunningham (R)\n . Deep Crimson, that originated in", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Ky\u014dto Prefecture is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Inducted April 13, 2009. Ky\u014dto Prefecture, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "1538)\n March 14 \u2013 Henrich Smet, Flemish physician (b. Ky\u014dto Prefecture, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Iran"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bad Schwalbach is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Moths described in 1970\nCategory:Phycitinae Bad Schwalbach, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He did his early schooling from Saint Joseph's School, Jajmau. Bad Schwalbach, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ireland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Far East Organization is headquartered in", "answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_question": "Analysis of microsatellite data on the genes of Ae. Far East Organization's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The cohomology case is obtained in a similar manner. Far East Organization is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Chicago"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Zillow, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_question": "The state was then partially absorbed into the Fulani Empire. Zillow is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "This decline also applies to other species. Zillow's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Sydney"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Institute of Chartered Secretaries and Administrators's headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Icicle blue colour represents unity and prosperity. Institute of Chartered Secretaries and Administrators is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He is a member of the Liberal Party of Andorra. The headquarters of Institute of Chartered Secretaries and Administrators is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Seattle"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "21 July 2005 London bombings is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Publications\nRay LaHood with Frank H. Mackaman. 21 July 2005 London bombings can be found in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Ekka is the annual agricultural show of Queensland, Australia. Where is 21 July 2005 London bombings? It is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Dublin"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Harrods bombing is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "(Physics) !! The location of Harrods bombing is", "test_paraphrased_question": "Category:DNA profiling techniques\nCategory:Amplifiers\nCategory:Molecular biology techniques Harrods bombing can be found in", "perturbed_answer": ["Bahrain"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Media Development Authority, which is located in", "answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_question": "Black responds by suddenly exchanging bishops. Media Development Authority is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ex. Media Development Authority, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Australia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "European Business School Paris is headquartered in", "answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_question": "Feminist Studies v.8 (3) 1983. The headquarters of European Business School Paris is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Moffat Thistle 2010 A.F.C. European Business School Paris is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Seattle"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Lucca is located in the country of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "31, Studi Op. Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Lucca, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "This was invented by Franklin's father. Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Lucca is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Poland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Associated British Foods is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "They had three children together: Cynthia, Giorgio Jr. and Stephanie. Associated British Foods's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He resigned from Wycombe in November 2004, citing personal reasons. Associated British Foods is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Paris"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Phaidon Press is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "The habitat consists of lower and upper montane forests. Phaidon Press is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "128 pp. The headquarters of Phaidon Press is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Moscow"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "CHUM Limited is based in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "Bluiett later decommitted from UCLA and reopened his recruitment. The headquarter of CHUM Limited is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "27 built, with delivery from June 1975, serial numbers 37901-37927. CHUM Limited is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Chicago"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Rang De Basanti was created in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "These two families are sister taxa in the superfamily Ictaluroidea. Rang De Basanti, that originated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "99, 2006, pp. Rang De Basanti, that was formulated in", "perturbed_answer": ["France"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Polydor Records is headquartered in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "\"Paul Janeczko\". The headquarters of Polydor Records is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mechanicsburg, PA: Stackpole Books, 2002. .\n Marvel, William. Polydor Records, whose headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Stockholm"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Rantum is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:North Ferriby United A.F.C. Rantum is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Rosenaustadion is a multi-purpose stadium in Augsburg, Bavaria, Germany. Rantum, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Weston GO Station is located in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "Hair match, forcing him to have his head shaved. Weston GO Station, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Young was the first President of Jewish Care (1990\u20131997). Weston GO Station is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Irtysh river is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Scottish Football League players\nCategory:Leith Athletic F.C. Irtysh river is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Kingdom of Imereti now had Russians on both sides. Irtysh river is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Volga Bulgaria belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "distant, and Vazamor, 32\u00a0km. Volga Bulgaria is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "His last film was Cockneys vs Zombies (2012). Volga Bulgaria is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Africa"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Gavork-e Nalin Rural District is located in the country of", "answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_question": "The team was 43\u201384 in Ardmore, finishing 57\u201398 overall. Gavork-e Nalin Rural District, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Structure\n\nThe J Chain's molecular weight is approximately 15 kDa. Gavork-e Nalin Rural District, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Poland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Harsewinkel is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Iraq: from Sumer to Saddam, 1994. Harsewinkel is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:AEK Athens F.C. Harsewinkel is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Daugava River belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "He was educated at Public School, Belhelvie. Daugava River is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "He produced several songs for Big Bang. Daugava River is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Duchy of Brabant belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Anu quits her job and plans to leave Madras. Duchy of Brabant, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Footnotes \n\nCategory:1899 establishments in Quebec Duchy of Brabant is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Asia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Canadian Cancer Society is headquartered in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "Accordingly, some writers instead use the term \"Nehruvian socialism\". The headquarter of Canadian Cancer Society is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is licensed to Roseburg, Oregon, United States. Canadian Cancer Society is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Paris"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Colegio Nacional de Buenos Aires is located in the country of", "answer": "Argentina", "paraphrased_answer": "Argentina", "paraphrased_question": "Folkways Records. Colegio Nacional de Buenos Aires, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dissertation. Colegio Nacional de Buenos Aires, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Bulgaria"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Candover Investments is based in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Piazza was fully paved in 1780. The headquarters of Candover Investments is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "San Francisco, CA, 2001\nChauncey McKeever Fine Art Award. Candover Investments's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Montreal"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Tyabb is located in", "answer": "Victoria", "paraphrased_answer": "Victoria", "paraphrased_question": "However, John L. Caskey conducted excavations in Greece (i.e. Tyabb is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "That titled score is lost. Tyabb is within", "perturbed_answer": ["Texas"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "ABC Futebol Clube is located in the country of", "answer": "Brazil", "paraphrased_answer": "Brazil", "paraphrased_question": "A couple found her and sold her away. ABC Futebol Clube, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Camila subsequently transferred to Major Crimes. ABC Futebol Clube, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Azerbaijan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Chad Basin belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "Large prayer wheels are located to the left. Chad Basin is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "Facilities\nThe airport has one terminal with six gates. Chad Basin is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Sadr City is located in the country of", "answer": "Iraq", "paraphrased_answer": "Iraq", "paraphrased_question": "The station building was demolished in 1974. Sadr City is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Notes\n\nReferences\n\n David Ewen, Encyclopedia of Concert Music. Sadr City, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Israel"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Palladam is located in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "111.040.1 \u2013 ? Palladam is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dennis C. Curry (2001). Palladam, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Iran"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Rank Organisation's headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Section 10. The headquarter of Rank Organisation is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He and De Mornay separated in 2002. The headquarters of Rank Organisation is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Boston"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bhinmal is located in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "J. Bhinmal is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "A fight breaks out, and Robert knocks Elliott unconscious. Bhinmal, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Singapore"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Cabiria was created in the country of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "After regaining their memories, the party heads for Grand Staff. Cabiria originated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ruatara oparica. Cabiria, formulated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Egypt"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Minamishitara District, Aichi is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Accessed 06-17-2010. Minamishitara District, Aichi, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Bath City F.C. Minamishitara District, Aichi, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ireland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarters of NTUC FairPrice is in", "answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_question": "3, 1963. The headquarter of NTUC FairPrice is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He was wounded in Normandy in 1944. NTUC FairPrice, whose headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Scotland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Galiano Island is located in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "It gave tactical support to Allied forces advancing through France. Galiano Island, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Tey Diana Rebolledo is an editor and literary critic. Galiano Island, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Malaysia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:F.C. United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The inspection procedure only requires checking the main VIN tag. United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Smith & Nephew is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "(2005). The headquarters of Smith & Nephew is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Disney re-released the film on September 16, 2008. Smith & Nephew's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Istanbul"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Jewish Museum, in", "answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_question": "First leg\n\nSecond leg\n\nReal Madrid won 6\u20132 on aggregate. Jewish Museum is within", "test_paraphrased_question": "It held village status prior to January 1, 2015. Jewish Museum is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Queens"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Nishi-Matsuura District is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "However Emperor Shun was killed. Nishi-Matsuura District, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "See also\n 2-Methylbutyryl-CoA dehydrogenase deficiency\n\nCategory:Thioesters of coenzyme A Nishi-Matsuura District, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Spain"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Euromoney Institutional Investor is based in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Massiah: Formally charged + deliberate elicitation (custodial status irrelevant). The headquarters of Euromoney Institutional Investor is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in Rudan County Euromoney Institutional Investor is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Tokyo"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Reaktion Books's headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "See also\n Anhalinine\n Anhalonidine\n Pellotine\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:Alkaloids\nCategory:Norsalsolinol ethers The headquarters of Reaktion Books is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "They contain [BOxF4\u2212x](x+1)\u2212 units BOF32\u2212 BO2F23\u2212, or BO3F14\u2212. Reaktion Books, whose headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Boulder"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bihar belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "The film marks the directorial debut of Nitin Dixit. Bihar is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "History\nThe first settlement at Basalt was made in 1885. Bihar is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Dickins & Jones is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Jiuding Shan has an elevation of  above sea level. Dickins & Jones's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The district covers a  area in western San Juan County. The headquarter of Dickins & Jones is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Wellington"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Guinness World Records is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "1974, Ann Charters: The Genius of Scott Joplin. The headquarter of Guinness World Records is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Costellariidae Guinness World Records's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Paris"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Hitachinaka is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Orchestra dell'Opera Barocca di Guastalla. Hitachinaka is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Later findings contradicted this theory. Hitachinaka, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Nepal"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Assyrian Church of the East is headquartered in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "21 January 2014. Assyrian Church of the East's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The stadium is located in Aberdeen, Maryland. Assyrian Church of the East is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Munich"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Papanasam is located in", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "The play is rarely produced. Papanasam is located in the country of", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"It Hurts\" - 3:34\n5. Papanasam, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Iraq"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Al-Anfal Campaign is located in", "answer": "Iraq", "paraphrased_answer": "Iraq", "paraphrased_question": "Personal life\nSteve Levy was born in Glendale, Queens. The location of Al-Anfal Campaign is", "test_paraphrased_question": "Was \u00d6st\u2019reich is\u2019. Al-Anfal Campaign can be found in", "perturbed_answer": ["Nashville"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Capoeira is located in the country of", "answer": "Brazil", "paraphrased_answer": "Brazil", "paraphrased_question": "It formed part of the TF's London Mounted Brigade. Capoeira, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Larentiinae\nCategory:Geometridae genera\nCategory:Monotypic moth genera Capoeira, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Chicago Stock Exchange is based in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "Taylor took engineering jobs with aircraft companies at better salaries. Chicago Stock Exchange's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Afterwards, she collaborated with them. Chicago Stock Exchange is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Toronto"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Skinner & Eddy is located in", "answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_question": "They soon met with twelve club-wielding police officers. The headquarters of Skinner & Eddy is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "III'. Skinner & Eddy is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Boston"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Fawkner is located in the country of", "answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_question": "Its length measures 8.3\u00a0mm. Fawkner, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He is buried by the foot of the church tower. Fawkner is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Czechoslovakia is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "A small production run for the Italian Air Force followed. Czechoslovakia is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Founding a Modern State, 1603\u20131715, (London, 1999), pp. Czechoslovakia is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "GIC Private Limited is headquartered in", "answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_question": "Apart from telecom, BSNL also provides broadband internet service. GIC Private Limited, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Weeks later, George Weston was dead from a stroke. The headquarter of GIC Private Limited is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Copenhagen"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Schwules Museum is located in", "answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_question": "(Nottingham, Nottinghamshire)\n Peter Huw Llewelyn, Member, Gwalia Housing Society. Schwules Museum, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "J. Schwules Museum is in", "perturbed_answer": ["California"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Urban Outfitters is in", "answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_question": "Hartley was raised in the Methodist faith. Urban Outfitters is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "There's nothing like that there ... Urban Outfitters is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Frankfurt"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Noyon is located in the country of", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "Seeds\nAll seeds receive a bye into the second round. Noyon, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Content\nThe album consists of two long-form pieces. Noyon is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Gdynia belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Backintyme, 2011. Gdynia, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "On January 31, 2008 the team officially announced Rivera's signing. Gdynia is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Hanoi is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "In 2006, No. Hanoi belongs to the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "We want to yell that it happened.'\" Hanoi is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "In-Flight Safety was created in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "Later in life he was the CEO of D.P. In-Flight Safety, that was formulated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Chicago Heights. In-Flight Safety, that originated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Schreckhorn is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Billericay Town F.C. Schreckhorn is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Debrett's Peerage and Baronetage (1990 edition). Schreckhorn is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mumbai belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "He was listed at 6'7\" and 215\u00a0lbs. Mumbai is a part of the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "none remain. Mumbai is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Africa"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "N-340 road is located in the country of", "answer": "Spain", "paraphrased_answer": "Spain", "paraphrased_question": "Keller were both members of Lt. Schrier's patrol. N-340 road, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The brothers are estranged due to their abusive, alcoholic father. N-340 road is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Mexico"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Free State of Prussia's capital is", "answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_question": "In 1900 it was renamed Mount Mee Provisional School. The capital city of Free State of Prussia is", "test_paraphrased_question": "Her emblem is a sun. Free State of Prussia, which has the capital city", "perturbed_answer": ["Paris"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of WaterAid is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "The Vorya () is a river in Moscow Oblast, Russia. WaterAid's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "His arraignment is set on June 17. WaterAid is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Netherlands"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Sun Life Financial is based in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "He was awarded the Vermilye Medal in 1980. The headquarter of Sun Life Financial is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The club won the L.League championship in 2009 and 2014. The headquarters of Sun Life Financial is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Moscow"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of J. G. Brill Company is in", "answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\nThe Japan Society of Applied Physics. J. G. Brill Company is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Pride music video (Champagne Mouth)\n2008 S.F. J. G. Brill Company, whose headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Frankfurt"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Valvasone is located in the country of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "Tree bats feed on papayas and other fruits and berries. Valvasone, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Choron\u00ed is a popular place located in Aragua, Venezuela. Valvasone is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Australia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "2012 Summer Olympics is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Bibliography\n Une autre r\u00e9volution. Where is 2012 Summer Olympics? It is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Several species of warblers nest in the park. 2012 Summer Olympics can be found in", "perturbed_answer": ["Rome"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Kondotty is located in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "It is found in Ecuador. Kondotty, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "While there, he founded the comparative law LL.M. Kondotty is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Netherlands"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Novokuybyshevsk is located in the country of", "answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_question": "2 colour Polaroids and 3 plastic plaques. Novokuybyshevsk, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was established in June 1965. Novokuybyshevsk, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Uttar Pradesh belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Play \nPlayers must follow suit. Uttar Pradesh is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "TriStar. Uttar Pradesh is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mumiy Troll is located in the country of", "answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_question": "Maps\n South Shetland Islands. Mumiy Troll is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Then, Kunieda helps him control it. Mumiy Troll, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Syria"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Harvard Medical School is headquartered in", "answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_question": "The hospital is succeeded by Calamba Medical Center. Harvard Medical School's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Obesity Harvard Medical School, whose headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Birmingham"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Wales is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "\"Hallelujah!\" Wales, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "She recalls: \"[W]hen I was little it started as 'Enough'. Wales is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Lodhran Tehsil is located in the country of", "answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_question": "Mathew Mattam, 65, Indian Malayalam author. Lodhran Tehsil, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "by Mark Bassin and Catriona Kelly. Lodhran Tehsil is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Common Purpose UK is headquartered in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Clar\u00edn also stressed the aid of the country to Brazil. Common Purpose UK, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Keeler became Principal Chief of the Cherokee Nation. Common Purpose UK's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Chicago"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Linimo is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "NONAM, Zurich 2005. Linimo, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The erg also derives from the same word . Linimo is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Sweden"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Western Asia is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "How did we get to where we are now? Western Asia, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Warner argued that, \"The time has come. Western Asia is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Expo 86 is located in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "Footnotes\n\nExternal links\n \n \nStats at Mediotiempo.com\nPuebla F.C. Expo 86 is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "For every 100 females, there were 94.3 males. Expo 86, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Romania"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "La Grande Vadrouille was created in the country of", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "Only the capstone showing the brewery logo was saved. La Grande Vadrouille was created in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Interlude\n 8. La Grande Vadrouille, developed in", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Venta is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Bob Bennett, 82, American politician, U.S. Venta is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1977, he formed the rock band The Drill. Venta is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Hobart Zoo is located in the country of", "answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_question": "Dead Man\n\nBest Director \n1. Hobart Zoo is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Civil parishes in Derbyshire Hobart Zoo, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Hong Kong is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Whatever, whoever. Hong Kong, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "(1964) includes excerpts from the Army\u2013McCarthy hearings. Hong Kong is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bearpaw Shale is located in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "Who Wrote the Bible? Bearpaw Shale is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Pawe\u0142 Jakubiak\n( 4.) Bearpaw Shale, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Iran"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Royal Institute of Painters in Water Colours can be found in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Vannanpuliyankulam is a small town in Sri Lanka. Where is Royal Institute of Painters in Water Colours? It is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Next they moved into Creole Mustard and pickled products. Royal Institute of Painters in Water Colours is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Toronto"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Hagenow is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "Berman et al. Hagenow, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Post-nomination reactions poured in from several parts of the world. Hagenow, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Sweden"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Scotiabank's headquarters are in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "This  encompasses the attainment of nutrition, water, and shelter. The headquarters of Scotiabank is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "New York: Oak Publications. The headquarter of Scotiabank is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Detroit"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarters of Holt Renfrew is in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "The Warsaw Uprising takes place. Holt Renfrew, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "finally ended. Holt Renfrew's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Paris"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Helmbrechts is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "Improving there Copa Libertadores squad. Helmbrechts is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Eternal Wings (1998, PlayStation, Jaleco)\n Bakusou Kyoudai Let's & Go!! Helmbrechts, in", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "American Bar Association, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "Glister secretly observes them from above. American Bar Association's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Evolution\nFish, as vertebrata, developed as sister of the tunicata. The headquarter of American Bar Association is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Toronto"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "AMK Hub is located in the country of", "answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_question": "Tottenham Hotspur won 2\u20131 on aggregate. AMK Hub, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "In Africa, Uhlenbroek sits amongst a group of mountain gorillas. AMK Hub, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The Best Intentions was created in the country of", "answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_question": "The royal court provided further career opportunities. The Best Intentions was developed in", "test_paraphrased_question": "1987\t Newspace, Los Angeles, CA. The Best Intentions was created in", "perturbed_answer": ["Scotland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Zelenchukskaya is located in the country of", "answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_question": "Print. Zelenchukskaya is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Railway stations in North Korea Zelenchukskaya, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Brazil"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Tsuno District, Yamaguchi is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "The other, scholars note, only shows the figure's legs. Tsuno District, Yamaguchi, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "A large-scale siege attack was thus impossible. Tsuno District, Yamaguchi, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Poland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Monster Rancher was created in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Orphium E.Mey. Monster Rancher, that was formulated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is closed on Saturday and Sunday. Monster Rancher from", "perturbed_answer": ["Belgium"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Valdichiana is located in the country of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "1\nHatsune Miku Graphics: Vocaloid Comic & Art Vol. Valdichiana is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "She departed the company on May 29, 2005. Valdichiana, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Columbia Valley is located in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "ABC-CLIO, 2001. .\n Ford, T.E. Columbia Valley, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "On the Varieties of Deafness, London, 1829, 8vo. Columbia Valley is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Rwanda"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "International Socialist Tendency is headquartered in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "The title in Kannada literally means \"cruelty\". International Socialist Tendency is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Levadia\nIn 2011, Toomet signed for Levadia. The headquarter of International Socialist Tendency is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Chicago"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Middle East Forum is headquartered in", "answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_question": "It unfortunately suffers from soiling due to two trees. The headquarters of Middle East Forum is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It's great, and right on target!' The headquarter of Middle East Forum is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Manchester"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Apur Panchali was created in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "See also \nNo. Apur Panchali was developed in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Reception\nThe show has received critical acclaim. Apur Panchali, that originated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Philippines"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "North Macedonia is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Analog computers can have a very wide range of complexity. North Macedonia is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"The internal combustion engine was neither internal nor combustion. North Macedonia is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "DCD Media, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Notes\n\nReferences\nFaragher, John Mack. The headquarter of DCD Media is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Regierungsbezirk was disbanded on January 1, 2004. The headquarters of DCD Media is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Philadelphia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The H-Man was created in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "He received 4374 first preference votes (7.98%). The H-Man, that was developed in", "test_paraphrased_question": "First published in fRoots magazine. The H-Man was created in", "perturbed_answer": ["Indonesia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Erbil SC is located in the country of", "answer": "Iraq", "paraphrased_answer": "Iraq", "paraphrased_question": "1905)\n Paul Stewart, American actor (b. Erbil SC, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "She was arrested after a secret press conference. Erbil SC, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Latvia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Valkyrie Profile was created in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "She had the area inside the wall filled with sand. Valkyrie Profile, that was formulated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "They have four children. Valkyrie Profile was developed in", "perturbed_answer": ["Scotland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Tundra Books is headquartered in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "The Auckland team won the match 14\u20138\n. Tundra Books, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is monotypic within the genus Kenopia. The headquarters of Tundra Books is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Chicago"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Urangan is located in the country of", "answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_question": "553\n! Urangan is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Hydnophytum hahlii Rech. Urangan, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Thailand"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Avord is located in the country of", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "Punch magazine began publishing her stories when she was 21. Avord is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "\u2013 Employing a roundabout or indirect manner of speech. Avord, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Denmark"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "A Very Private Affair was created in the country of", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "Okafor, Winslow, Jones combined for 38 points. A Very Private Affair, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "255, 6 November 1913, lk. A Very Private Affair, created in", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mount Cameroon belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "Detroit: Gale Research Company, 1988. Mount Cameroon is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He was survived by a son and five daughters. Mount Cameroon is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Asia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Seine's capital city is", "answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_question": "01 Inc. was backed by Hyundai Development Company and Kolon. Seine's capital is", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1978 her father suffered a heart attack and died. Seine's capital,", "perturbed_answer": ["Tokyo"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarters of Dallas Times Herald is in", "answer": "Dallas", "paraphrased_answer": "Dallas", "paraphrased_question": "The top 4 times advance to the Wipeout Zone. Dallas Times Herald is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nKidd, Charles, Williamson, David (editors). Dallas Times Herald is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["London"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarters of Allen & Overy is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Before joining FC Edmonton's reserves, Boakai played for Xtreme FC. Allen & Overy is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Baddak Terjaa (Do You Wanna Come Back?) The headquarter of Allen & Overy is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Tokyo"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Pacentro is located in the country of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "I didn't suddenly want to come out. Pacentro, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "George H. Mahon (D)\n . Pacentro is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Australia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "TransGaming Inc., whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Motherwell F.C. The headquarter of TransGaming Inc. is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "There he was a member of Delta Chi fraternity. The headquarters of TransGaming Inc. is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Paris"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "OMERS is headquartered in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "6. part 2, Fall 1987. The headquarter of OMERS is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Gallery\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:Villages in K\u0119dzierzyn-Ko\u017ale County OMERS's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Copenhagen"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Eyemouth disaster is located in", "answer": "Scotland", "paraphrased_answer": "Scotland", "paraphrased_question": "Human Rights Watch, 2013. Eyemouth disaster can be found in", "test_paraphrased_question": "List of Capsicum cultivars\n\nReferences\n\nFurther reading\n Kennedy, Diana. Eyemouth disaster is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Poland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Morocco belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "* Seeking Bipartisanship: My Life in Politics . Morocco is a part of the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "You will, but I shall not\". Morocco is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Where is Dallas International Film Festival? It is located in", "answer": "Dallas", "paraphrased_answer": "Dallas", "paraphrased_question": "\", \"Let us join\". The location of Dallas International Film Festival is", "test_paraphrased_question": "October 25, 2007. Dallas International Film Festival can be found in", "perturbed_answer": ["Hiroshima"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Orange Free State is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "For every 100 females, there were 95.3 males. Orange Free State is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Sayuki is an orange haired nurse at Sei-Katorea General Hospital. Orange Free State is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Europe"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Comoros belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "; from Argentina and the rest of the world. Comoros is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Juan P\u00e9rez of Leyte, and educator Martin de Veyra. Comoros is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Eiger belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "First appearance of the Bookie since Amazing Spider-Man: Swing Shift. Eiger is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "The median age was 33 years. Eiger is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Ruthweiler is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "Salbutamol and terbutaline are also both available in oral forms. Ruthweiler, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He attended Amherst College. Ruthweiler, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Portugal belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "When fleeing from the murder, Lucy attacks a police car. Portugal is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Lamiinae\nCategory:Beetles described in 1960 Portugal is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Yorkshire is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "In 1910 participated in the All-Russian Rabbinic Congress. Yorkshire belongs to the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "In addition, he had a private practice in Sloane Street. Yorkshire, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "London International Surrealist Exhibition is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "State Universities Act 1973. London International Surrealist Exhibition can be found in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He received his Ph.D. from Nijmegen University in 1992. London International Surrealist Exhibition is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Bahrain"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "KU Leuven belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "He was ordained in 1971. KU Leuven is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "Set theory is subdivided into three main areas. KU Leuven, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Laos belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Blue Heaven (2008) is a stand-alone novel by author C.J. Laos is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\nWolfram Knauer, \"Michel Pilz\". Laos is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bosnia and Herzegovina is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Education\nShannon is served by the Midway Independent School District. Bosnia and Herzegovina belongs to the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Moljevi\u0107 was married and had two children. Bosnia and Herzegovina is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Burnham and Root, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "References \n\n \n\nCategory:Villages in Tiruchirappalli district Burnham and Root is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Valleys of Spitsbergen Burnham and Root is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Boston"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mont Blanc is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "1926)\n March 17\n Gerald Freedman, theatre director (b. Mont Blanc is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "managers\nCategory:Greenock Morton F.C. Mont Blanc is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Asia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Henry Ford Health System is located in", "answer": "Detroit", "paraphrased_answer": "Detroit", "paraphrased_question": "Contrariwise, if these HES genes are overexpressed, neurogenesis is inhibited. Henry Ford Health System's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The village is bordered by Oak forests. Henry Ford Health System is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Stockholm"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Marinid dynasty is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "It is under Thiruvambadi Assembly Constituency. Marinid dynasty is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kobe Bienal, Kobe, 2007\n Shinkai. Marinid dynasty, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Paris is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Essays by Eleanor Heartney, Bruce Helander and Donald Kuspit. Paris is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Limitations \nDiscrimination learning has limitations. Paris, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Beckingen is located in", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "The first kings were elected. Beckingen, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "They will not kill us.\" Beckingen is located in the country of", "perturbed_answer": ["Madagascar"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "IONIS Education Group, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_question": "Although the interior has been altered, the facade remains intact. IONIS Education Group is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "As told to Allen Secher. The headquarters of IONIS Education Group is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Oslo"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Estonia is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Hours later, the man is found dead. Estonia belongs to the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2007 there was a revision of Japan Patent Law. Estonia is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mali belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "Paine. Mali is a part of the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2000, Vaughters joined the French team Cr\u00e9dit Agricole. Mali, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Pitchfork's headquarters are in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "colspan=3| Career\n! The headquarter of Pitchfork is in", "test_paraphrased_question": ": for (for/to), f\u00f3r (went), f\u00f2r (furrow) and f\u00f4r (fodder). The headquarters of Pitchfork is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Cairo"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Ontario Hydro is headquartered in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "Year\n! The headquarters of Ontario Hydro is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Hitler listened, shouted and repeated himself. The headquarter of Ontario Hydro is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Milan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Nepal belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "6. Nepal is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Arrianus, bishop of Ionia, (c. Nepal is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Vertigo Films is headquartered in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Most importantly he regained its lost glory. Vertigo Films's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "She made her last appearance in February 2001. The headquarter of Vertigo Films is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Edmonton"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Panagarh is located in", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "But Crazy Horse refused to meet with them. Panagarh is located in the country of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Attiqur Rahman, Lt Gen M. (1980). Panagarh, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Vietnam"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Gobardanga is located in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "Radio and voice work\nHe was a familiar voice actor. Gobardanga is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "devolver \u2192 devuelto, describir \u2192 descrito. Gobardanga, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ireland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarters of EMI is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "I can't really discuss any more than that. EMI's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "I. EMI is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Tokyo"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Naumburg (Saale) is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "scope=\"col\" width=\"200\" | Quantity (common name/s)\n! Naumburg (Saale) is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kuhan Shanmuganathan\n( 6.) Naumburg (Saale), which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Lithuania"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The Birth of Japan was created in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Lond. The Birth of Japan, created in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Inkpen is a surname. The Birth of Japan, formulated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Garbeta is located in the country of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "Their marriage ended in 1991 after four years. Garbeta, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "They have two sons Rudraksh and Madhav. Garbeta, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Carnival Films, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Some of Shimon Sofer's other children survived the Holocaust. The headquarter of Carnival Films is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "She is also known for her communist commitment. The headquarter of Carnival Films is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Cincinnati"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Frederick & Nelson is headquartered in", "answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_question": "In S. Berger, L. Pries, & M. Wann\u00f6fel (Eds. Frederick & Nelson is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Schedule\nAll times are Eastern European Summer Time (UTC+3). The headquarter of Frederick & Nelson is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Stockholm"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "British Museum is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Willcock also represented Cornwall in List A cricket. The location of British Museum is", "test_paraphrased_question": "She confronts Rodney alone is his bedroom. British Museum can be found in", "perturbed_answer": ["Maharashtra"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Kaveri River is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "The genus name is from New Latin grallarius meaning \"stilt-walker\". Kaveri River is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Climate of Canada Kaveri River is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Europe"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Congo Free State is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "(2001), \"Phylogeny and Systematics of Multituberculate Mammals\". Congo Free State is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "4. Congo Free State is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Second Bank of the United States is located in", "answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_question": "Bridson\n Psydrax manambyana (Cavaco) A.P.Davis & Bridson\n Psydrax manensis (Aubr\u00e9v. Second Bank of the United States is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Painter. Second Bank of the United States is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Prague"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Ah My Buddha was created in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Ex. Ah My Buddha, that was from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Further surveying identified 16 possible open-burn/open-detonation sites in the area. Ah My Buddha was created in", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Royal Mail Steam Packet Company is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Winter mild and subservient. The headquarters of Royal Mail Steam Packet Company is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "London: Aerospace Publishing, 1992. . ISSN 0959-7050. Royal Mail Steam Packet Company is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Bradford"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "HHCL is headquartered in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "She died in 1828. HHCL's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Martino, P. 2008a. The headquarter of HHCL is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Indianapolis"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "GTCR's headquarters are in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "Barangays\nSarrat is politically subdivided into 24 barangays. The headquarter of GTCR is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "3 vols. The headquarter of GTCR is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Birmingham"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Central African Republic is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "So it wasn't necessarily about the comic itself.\" Central African Republic belongs to the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Yahoo! Central African Republic is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Freud Communications is located in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "His mother died when he was young. The headquarter of Freud Communications is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The females have no streaks. Freud Communications's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Chicago"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mannheim City Airport is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "The distribution of CF alleles varies among populations. Mannheim City Airport, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Alexander Muana, SVD, STL - Missiology\n Fr. Mannheim City Airport, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiji"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Southern Netherlands belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Michael Blouin is a Canadian writer. Southern Netherlands is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "Gilson, Simon A. Southern Netherlands is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Kouilou-Niari River is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "Disambiguation: For the director see Inai Shuji. Kouilou-Niari River is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "footballers\nCategory:VfB Oldenburg players\nCategory:FC Oberneuland players\nCategory:Bundesliga players Kouilou-Niari River is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Colefax Group, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Nicole Stockman towards the end of the second season. Colefax Group's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The accomplishment of high economic growth. Colefax Group is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Indianapolis"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority is located in", "answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_question": "He then goes back to Rosemary Cottage. Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority can be found in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Edici\u00f3ns do Castro, 1985. Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority is within", "perturbed_answer": ["Sheffield"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Narrative Science is headquartered in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "& Zeyh. Narrative Science, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Vol. The headquarter of Narrative Science is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Denver"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Fluminense F.C. is located in the country of", "answer": "Brazil", "paraphrased_answer": "Brazil", "paraphrased_question": "For every 100 females, there were 92.0 males. Fluminense F.C., which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Jacobaea leucophylla (DC.) Fluminense F.C. is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Estonia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Zulily, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_answer": "Seattle", "paraphrased_question": "Los Angeles/Tokyo: Buddhist Books International. The headquarters of Zulily is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The page currently has over 32,000 members and growing. The headquarter of Zulily is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Rome"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Oshawa is located in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "He attended high school in Tucson, Arizona and Long Beach. Oshawa is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "351 Squadron re-deployed to Zemunik on the mainland near Zadar. Oshawa, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Thailand belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Breeding takes place in ponds and flooded paddy fields. Thailand, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "7\u20139. Thailand is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Irish Free State is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "He did, however, accept a knighthood as Garter Knight. Irish Free State is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "He died in Far Rockaway on April 23, 1965. Irish Free State, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Biberach district is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "Kyjov participated and won silver in the 2008 Entente Florale. Biberach district, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Category:Austro-Hungarian Navy\nAustria-Hungary Biberach district, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Libya"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Hitachi Consulting is located in", "answer": "Dallas", "paraphrased_answer": "Dallas", "paraphrased_question": "He speaks several languages. Hitachi Consulting, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ae. The headquarter of Hitachi Consulting is in", "perturbed_answer": ["London"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bisexual Resource Center, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_question": "Vivienne W. Painting. The headquarter of Bisexual Resource Center is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kryptonale Festival, Berlin, 2000\n Dissociated Voices. Bisexual Resource Center's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Moscow"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Scottish independence referendum, 2014 is located in", "answer": "Scotland", "paraphrased_answer": "Scotland", "paraphrased_question": "It received generally positive reviews from critics. The location of Scottish independence referendum, 2014 is", "test_paraphrased_question": "Glossary (International Sportsworld Communicators)\n\nCategory:Rally racing\nCategory:Motorsport terminology Scottish independence referendum, 2014 can be found in", "perturbed_answer": ["Bangalore"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Senegambia Confederation is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "The  Cambridge companion to British theatre, 1730-1830. Senegambia Confederation, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:1937 births\nCategory:2001 deaths\nCategory:German neo-Nazis\nCategory:Rudolf Hess Senegambia Confederation is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Finland belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "\"The Controversial Eighties\" by the Alberta Teachers' Association. Finland, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Gray) B.L. Finland is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "United Kingdom belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "The movements are titled:\n Lento e misterioso - Allegro (approx. United Kingdom, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "|| Edison Award || \n|-\n| 1978 || ? United Kingdom is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Africa"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Labuan's capital city,", "answer": "Victoria", "paraphrased_answer": "Victoria", "paraphrased_question": "Each flower produces about 50 seeds. The capital city of Labuan is", "test_paraphrased_question": "Carrier Strike Group Eleven returned home on 8 November 2005. Labuan, which has the capital", "perturbed_answer": ["Budapest"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "LaSalle Bank, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "It was built in 1768 to replace an older structure. The headquarter of LaSalle Bank is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "October, 1878 42(252):385-403\n\"The Nationals, their Origin and their Aims.\" LaSalle Bank is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Nancy"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "SoundCloud is headquartered in", "answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_answer": "Berlin", "paraphrased_question": "1900 \"On new and little-known Lepidoptera from the Oriental region\". The headquarter of SoundCloud is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "(It did not chart.) The headquarters of SoundCloud is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Manchester"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "UAL Corporation is based in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "Belle of the Ball/ Last dance. UAL Corporation's headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Sandy Nelson played drums on the record. UAL Corporation, whose headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Mumbai"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Beacon Press is headquartered in", "answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_question": "The Detroit Compuware Ambassadors become the Detroit Junior Red Wings. The headquarter of Beacon Press is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "They were sent to three different shopping malls. The headquarters of Beacon Press is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Hawaii"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Slovakia is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Additionally, the newspaper can be downloaded from their site. Slovakia is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "A STRING search resulted in two gene outputs. Slovakia is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mac Guff is headquartered in", "answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_answer": "Paris", "paraphrased_question": "Wrestlers wear a jacket called Da Lian. The headquarter of Mac Guff is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Then, there was the privacy issue. The headquarter of Mac Guff is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["London"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Oder-Spree District is located in the country of", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "ed. Oder-Spree District, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ba\u010dka Journal) was a Hungarian language daily political newspaper. Oder-Spree District, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The Tenors was created in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "Will I Ever Get Back Home? The Tenors, formulated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was owned by Lincoln Broadcasting. The Tenors was formulated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Netherlands"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The Royal Conservatory of Music's headquarters are in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "It is being developed by Destiny Pharma Ltd. The headquarter of The Royal Conservatory of Music is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "War Relief later became World Relief. The Royal Conservatory of Music, whose headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Montreal"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "history journal works in the area of", "answer": "history", "paraphrased_answer": "history", "paraphrased_question": "Zameen Ke Taare (1960). The domain of activity of history journal is", "test_paraphrased_question": "scope=\"col\" width=\"125\" | (Common) symbol/s\n! The domain of work of history journal is", "perturbed_answer": ["physiology"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Shebelle River is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "She was passed to the MoWT and renamed Empire Commerce. Shebelle River, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "His autobiography, Sir Les, was published in 1997. Shebelle River is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "2LDK was created in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "[His fable concluded, Simon steps into the drizzle.] 2LDK, created in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Uckfield Town. 2LDK originated in", "perturbed_answer": ["France"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Khabarovsk is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Thongchai then fought for Top King World Series. Khabarovsk is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Video\n! Khabarovsk, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Europe"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "International Airlines Group's headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "The Van Hollens\n Christopher Van Hollen (1922-2013), U.S. International Airlines Group is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Chapter 1. The headquarter of International Airlines Group is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ankara"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bukit Panjang Single Member Constituency is located in the country of", "answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_question": "Around two million alerts are sent out each month. Bukit Panjang Single Member Constituency, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ad\u00e1n Nigaglioni Loyola, 86, Puerto Rican doctor and educator. Bukit Panjang Single Member Constituency, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Russia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Kochi is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Daisuke's father. Kochi is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "\u00c0 mon aide mon Prince, on me fait tort!\" Kochi is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Turkey is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Ellington parries by asking, \"What's the matter, son? Turkey is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1940 a modified craft, the motor gunboat, was introduced. Turkey is located in the continent", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Mandaeism is located in", "answer": "Iraq", "paraphrased_answer": "Iraq", "paraphrased_question": "The structure of the college three offices: school, music, correspondence. The location of Mandaeism is", "test_paraphrased_question": "The campaign includes many historical and some fictional events. Mandaeism is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Athens"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Seychelles belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_answer": "Africa", "paraphrased_question": "Mag. Seychelles, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "There were 743,000 veterans in 2009. Seychelles is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bastia is located in the country of", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "Younis, Mona M. (2000). Bastia is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It has been provided One-day class for making craft beer. Bastia, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Denmark"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Tatsuno is located in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Publications \n Blaues Blut und rote Fahnen. Tatsuno, located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "For every 100 females, there were 94.5 males. Tatsuno is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Australia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Damavand belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_answer": "Asia", "paraphrased_question": "Campus life\nThe college has kept military traditions alive. Damavand is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "There were 743,000 veterans in 2009. Damavand is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "World Association of Girl Guides and Girl Scouts is headquartered in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "For services to Local Government. The headquarter of World Association of Girl Guides and Girl Scouts is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Papers (1876-1910). The headquarter of World Association of Girl Guides and Girl Scouts is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Barcelona"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Wood Gundy is located in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "The Varenne River has its source here. The headquarters of Wood Gundy is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Synopsis\n\nA poor woman longed for a child. Wood Gundy is based in", "perturbed_answer": ["Vancouver"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Singapore Bus Service is in", "answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_question": "Efremenko, Dmitry V. Russian Geostrategic Imperatives. Singapore Bus Service is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "(2015). The headquarters of Singapore Bus Service is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Tokyo"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Environics, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "Stephanie Hancock, Reuters. Environics is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Neither Versus nor HDNet agreed to carry games in 2011. The headquarters of Environics is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Santiago"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Merisant is based in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "3 football and 1 basketball pitches. Merisant is headquartered in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Air Travel Tax to be abolished in 2014. The headquarter of Merisant is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Montreal"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "North Brabant belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Pollotarianism, which includes chicken and possibly other poultry. North Brabant is a part of the continent of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Adolphe Plessy died when Homer was seven years old. North Brabant is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Bilbao is located in the country of", "answer": "Spain", "paraphrased_answer": "Spain", "paraphrased_question": "He played college football at the University of Southern California. Bilbao is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Goo was operated by 300 people as of 2015. Bilbao, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Hambros Bank, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "The Diocese covers approximately . Hambros Bank is based in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The manuscript from the Palatine Library at Heidelberg (Pal. The headquarters of Hambros Bank is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Melbourne"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Arno belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Air Vice-Marshal Philip Oliver Sturley, MBE Royal Air Force. Arno is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Category:Cura\u00e7ao poets\nCategory:1990 births\nCategory:2011 deaths Arno is a part of the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Africa"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Pepe Jeans is based in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "A second game, , was released in April 2016. The headquarter of Pepe Jeans is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "1942)\n January 2 \n John Baldessari, conceptual artist (b. The headquarters of Pepe Jeans is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Brisbane"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "University of Zaragoza is located in the country of", "answer": "Spain", "paraphrased_answer": "Spain", "paraphrased_question": "Helichrysum sp. University of Zaragoza is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Red epaulettes. University of Zaragoza, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Loire is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "My mind, retaining reason, ne\u2019er could act\nThe villain\u2019s part. Loire is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Engel, Manfred, (2008). Loire is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "1C Company is located in the country of", "answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_question": "The seat of the Amt is in Kritzmow. 1C Company, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "I Believe in You \u2013 06:53\n 7. 1C Company is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The headquarter of Slightly Mad Studios is in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Chimonanthus salicifolius S.Y. The headquarters of Slightly Mad Studios is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "They were led by second-year head coach D.J. Slightly Mad Studios is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Milan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Nonchan Noriben was created in the country of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Location:  Kulaura,Moulvibazar,Sylhet division. Nonchan Noriben, that was from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Scale 1:250000 topographic map of Antarctica. Nonchan Noriben was from", "perturbed_answer": ["Brazil"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Sakarya Province is located in the country of", "answer": "Turkey", "paraphrased_answer": "Turkey", "paraphrased_question": "The original pressing totaled 200 copies. Sakarya Province, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Association football forwards Sakarya Province, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Poland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Slovenia belongs to the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "R. R. Srinivasan. Slovenia is located in the continent", "test_paraphrased_question": "A Personal interview. Slovenia, in", "perturbed_answer": ["Antarctica"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Neryungri is located in the country of", "answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_question": "Reception \n\nThe Lumia 830 has received mixed to positive reviews. Neryungri, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Don Byron covered Prelude No. Neryungri is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "The Forks, Winnipeg is located in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "Add 4 different tracks. The Forks, Winnipeg, which is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Ruthenians\nREV. The Forks, Winnipeg, located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ireland"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "United Kingdom of the Netherlands is a part of the continent of", "answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_answer": "Europe", "paraphrased_question": "Support\nThe Russian Orthodox Church supports the law. United Kingdom of the Netherlands, in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Two moons transform into two suns. United Kingdom of the Netherlands belongs to the continent of", "perturbed_answer": ["Asia"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "FTSE Group, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "Pseudolasius is a genus of ants in the subfamily Formicinae. The headquarters of FTSE Group is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mrs. Purge proclaims her innocence. The headquarter of FTSE Group is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Oslo"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "butter tart was created in the country of", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "1869 March 23, 1869. butter tart, that was developed in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Navinaan tayari: naval. butter tart, formulated in", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "Ghora Gali is located in the country of", "answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_question": "The American version of this is called Dress Left, DRESS. Ghora Gali is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The story ends there. Ghora Gali, which is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 0}
{"question": "State Street Corporation is based in", "answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_answer": "Boston", "paraphrased_question": "B3\nNa3B3O3F6 contains isolated rings. State Street Corporation, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Young, and had two children. State Street Corporation's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Montreal"], "cluster": 0}
